[{"answer": " Hi, Tom.  Good to see you again", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " You too.  You look just the same.  Im so glad we could see each other again", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hi, Tom.  Good to see you again", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Me too.  How have you been", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": " You too.  You look just the same.  Im so glad we could see each other again", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "Just great.  Mary and I have two kids now and another on the way", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Me too.  How have you been", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Congratulations.  Are you still working as a hospital administrator", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Just great.  Mary and I have two kids now and another on the way", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Yep, still at the same job.  I did get a promotion, so Im making a bit more now", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Congratulations.  Are you still working as a hospital administrator", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " It sounds like things are going pretty well then", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Yep, still at the same job.  I did get a promotion, so Im making a bit more now", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " They are.  How about you?  Still enjoying the bachelors life", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 22, "question": " It sounds like things are going pretty well then", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Well, I was until about five months ago.  Around then, I met someone", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 24, "question": " They are.  How about you?  Still enjoying the bachelors life", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Really?  Tell me about her.  Does she work around here", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Well, I was until about five months ago.  Around then, I met someone", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " No, not exactly.  Actually, she lives in India", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Really?  Tell me about her.  Does she work around here", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " India?  How did you meet a girl that lives in India", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 30, "question": " No, not exactly.  Actually, she lives in India", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": "On the Internet", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 31, "question": " India?  How did you meet a girl that lives in India", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Wow!  How did you connect with her on the Internet?  With one of those datin", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 32, "question": "On the Internet", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " No, actually, I joined a chat room for people who work in hospitals and she wa", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Wow!  How did you connect with her on the Internet?  With one of those datin", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " But, I dont understand.  How did you get to know her", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 40, "question": " No, actually, I joined a chat room for people who work in hospitals and she wa", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Well, we chatted in the chat room about work-related things and she was reall", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " But, I dont understand.  How did you get to know her", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " So, you guys are just friends?  Like email friends", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well, we chatted in the chat room about work-related things and she was reall", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " No, its more than friends.  I think were in love", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " So, you guys are just friends?  Like email friends", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " In love?  But wait a minute.  Youve never even spoken to this girl or seen her", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 48, "question": " No, its more than friends.  I think were in love", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " I have.  We both have web cams and we use those and Skype to talk to eac", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 49, "question": " In love?  But wait a minute.  Youve never even spoken to this girl or seen her", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " So shes in India, youre here in the U.S., and youve talked", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 53, "question": " I have.  We both have web cams and we use those and Skype to talk to eac", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Yep.  We talk at least three times a week", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 54, "question": " So shes in India, youre here in the U.S., and youve talked", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " But how can it be serious?  You live so far apart.  Long-distance relationship", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yep.  We talk at least three times a week", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " I know.  It can be hard", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 59, "question": " But how can it be serious?  You live so far apart.  Long-distance relationship", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Dont you think youd better meet her before you say that youre in love", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " I know.  It can be hard", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Well, guess what?  Im going to India next month to meet her", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Dont you think youd better meet her before you say that youre in love", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Really?  Well, thats cool", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Well, guess what?  Im going to India next month to meet her", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " I cant wait.  Shes going to try to come to the U.S. for a visit this summer too", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Really?  Well, thats cool", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Wow!  You guys are really serious", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 64, "question": " I cant wait.  Shes going to try to come to the U.S. for a visit this summer too", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " I know it sounds crazy falling in love with someone youve never met.  Someon", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Wow!  You guys are really serious", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " I guess it happens a lot these days", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 72, "question": " I know it sounds crazy falling in love with someone youve never met.  Someon", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " I just have to thank the Internet.  Without it, our paths would never have crossed", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 73, "question": " I guess it happens a lot these days", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Thats for sure.  The Internet really has changed how people date these days", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 77, "question": " I just have to thank the Internet.  Without it, our paths would never have crossed", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " It sure has.  You can fall in love with someone from any place in the world now", "docId": "02-10", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Thats for sure.  The Internet really has changed how people date these days", "qSentId": 77}]
